<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_label">[Çåŕŕîéŕ Šéţûþ one two]</string>
    <string name="suw_back_button_label">[βåçķ one]</string>
    <string name="suw_more_button_label">[Ḿöŕé one]</string>
    <string name="suw_next_button_label">[Ñéхţ one]</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_button">[ÅçţîVåţé one two]</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_continue">[Çöñţîñûé one two]</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_error_lookup">"[Šöŕŕý, ŵé'ŕé ĥåVîñĝ ţŕöûɓļé åçţîVåţîñĝ ýöûŕ þĥöñé. Çöñţåçţ çûšţöḿéŕ šéŕVîçé åţ (800) 922-0204. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen]"</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_error_lost_stolen">"[Šöŕŕý, ŵé'ŕé ĥåVîñĝ ţŕöûɓļé åçţîVåţîñĝ ýöûŕ þĥöñé. Þļéåšé çåļļ (877) 807-4646 ƒŕöḿ åñöţĥéŕ þĥöñé ţö åçţîVåţé ýöûŕ 4Ĝ ĻŢÉ šéŕVîçé åñð ţĥéñ ţŕý åĝåîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six]"</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_error_network">[Ḿåķé šûŕé ýöû ĥåVé å ĝööð šîĝñåļ (ḿûļţîþļé ɓåŕš) åñð ţŕý åĝåîñ. Îƒ ţĥîš þŕöɓļéḿ þéŕšîšţš, þļéåšé çöñţåçţ çûšţöḿéŕ šéŕVîçé åţ (800) 922-0204 ƒöŕ åššîšţåñçé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_error_not_retryable">"[Šöŕŕý, ŵé'ŕé ĥåVîñĝ ţŕöûɓļé åçţîVåţîñĝ ýöûŕ þĥöñé. Çöñţåçţ çûšţöḿéŕ šéŕVîçé åţ (800) 922-0204. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen]"</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_error_pin">[Åççöûñţ ÞÎÑ ðöéš ñöţ ḿåţçĥ. Þļéåšé ţŕý åĝåîñ. one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_error_release">[Ţö åçţîVåţé ýöûŕ þĥöñé, çåļļ (800) 922-0204 ƒŕöḿ åñöţĥéŕ þĥöñé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_error_restricted">[Ţö åçţîVåţé ýöûŕ þĥöñé, ƒöļļöŵ ţĥé îñšţŕûçţîöñš îñçļûðéð ŵîţĥ ýöûŕ ñéŵ þĥöñé öŕ çöñţåçţ ţĥé νéŕîžöñ Ŵîŕéļéšš åðḿîñîšţŕåţöŕ åţ ýöûŕ öŕĝåñîžåţîöñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_error_restricted_title">[Ĥöŵ ţö åçţîVåţé ýöûŕ þĥöñé one two three four]</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_error_ssn">[Šöçîåļ Šéçûŕîţý ñûḿɓéŕ ðöéš ñöţ ḿåţçĥ. Þļéåšé ţŕý åĝåîñ. one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_error_title">"[Çåñ'ţ åçţîVåţé one two three]"</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_exiting">[Éхîţîñĝ åçţîVåţîöñ. one two three]</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_notification">[Ţåþ ţö åçţîVåţé ýöûŕ þĥöñé one two three four]</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_notification_title">[Ŕéåðý ţö åçţîVåţé one two three]</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_progress">[Þļéåšé ŵåîţ ŵĥîļé ŵé þŕéþåŕé ýöûŕ þĥöñé. one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_ready_new">[Ţĥîš ḿåý ţåķé å ƒéŵ ḿîñûţéš one two three four]</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_ready_title">[Ŕéåðý ţö åçţîVåţé¿ one two three]</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_ready_upgrade">"[βéƒöŕé ýöû åçţîVåţé ţĥîš þĥöñé, ɓåçķ ûþ ýöûŕ çöñţåçţš åñð ţûŕñ öƒƒ ýöûŕ öļð þĥöñé.

Öñçé ýöû šţåŕţ åçţîVåţîöñ, ŵé'ļļ ţŕåñšƒéŕ ýöûŕ ñûḿɓéŕ ţö ţĥîš þĥöñé åñð ðéåçţîVåţé ýöûŕ öļð þĥöñé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]"</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_retry">[Ŕéţŕý one]</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_skip">[Šķîþ one]</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_success">[Ýöûŕ νéŕîžöñ þĥöñé îš ñöŵ åçţîVé. Ýöûŕ ñûḿɓéŕ îš %1$s one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_success_title">[Þĥöñé åçţîVåţéð one two three]</string>
    <string name="vzw_activate_title">[Þĥöñé åçţîVåţîöñ one two three]</string>
    <string name="vzw_activating_new_title">[Ĝéţţîñĝ þĥöñé ñûḿɓéŕ… one two three]</string>
    <string name="vzw_activating_upgrade">[Ţö ţŕåñšƒéŕ ýöûŕ ñûḿɓéŕ ţö ýöûŕ ñéŵ þĥöñé, ýöûŕ öļð þĥöñé ñééðš ţö ɓé ţûŕñéð öƒƒ. one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="vzw_activating_upgrade_title">[Ţŕåñšƒéŕŕîñĝ þĥöñé ñûḿɓéŕ… one two three four]</string>
    <string name="vzw_cold_notification">[Çöñţåçţ νéŕîžöñ ţö åçţîVåţé ýöûŕ þĥöñé. one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="vzw_data_limit">[Ýöûŕ ðåţå ûšåĝé îš çûŕŕéñţļý ļîḿîţéð ðûé ţö ţîḿé öƒ ðåý öŕ å ðåţå ļîḿîţ. Ýöû ŵîļļ ñééð ţö ûšé Ŵî-Fî ţö çöñţîñûé šéţţîñĝ ûþ ýöûŕ ðéVîçé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="vzw_data_limit_title">[Ðåţå ûšåĝé ļîḿîţéð one two three]</string>
    <string name="vzw_data_redirected">"[Ýöû ðöñ'ţ ĥåVé å νéŕîžöñ Ŵîŕéļéšš þļåñ öŕ ýöû'Vé ûšéð åļļ öƒ ýöûŕ þļåñ åļļöŵåñçé, þļéåšé çöñţåçţ νéŕîžöñ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]"</string>
    <string name="vzw_data_redirected_title">[Ĝéţ νéŕîžöñ šéŕVîçé one two three]</string>
    <string name="vzw_data_restricted">[Ðûé ţö ţîḿé öƒ ðåý öŕ å ðåţå ļîḿîţ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="vzw_data_restricted_title">[Ðåţå ûšåĝé ļîḿîţéð one two three]</string>
    <string name="vzw_later_button">[Ļåţéŕ one]</string>
    <string name="vzw_no_mobile_data_connection">[Åðð ðåţå öŕ ŕöåḿîñĝ þļåñ ţĥŕöûĝĥ νéŕîžöñ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="vzw_no_mobile_data_connection_title">[Ñö ḿöɓîļé ðåţå çöññéçţîöñ one two three]</string>
    <string name="vzw_setup_app_label">[νéŕîžöñ Åççöûñţ ÅçţîVåţîöñ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="vzw_verify_button">[νéŕîƒý one two]</string>
    <string name="vzw_verify_pin">"[Ţö ĝéţ šţåŕţéð, éñţéŕ ýöûŕ åççöûñţ'š ÞÎÑ: one two three four five]"</string>
    <string name="vzw_verify_progress_title">[νéŕîƒýîñĝ ýöûŕ åççöûñţ… one two three]</string>
    <string name="vzw_verify_ssn">"[Ţö ĝéţ šţåŕţéð, éñţéŕ ţĥé ļåšţ 4 ðîĝîţš öƒ ýöûŕ åççöûñţ öŵñéŕ'š Šöçîåļ Šéçûŕîţý ñûḿɓéŕ: one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen]"</string>
    <string name="vzw_verify_switch_pin">[Ûšé åççöûñţ ÞÎÑ îñšţéåð one two three]</string>
    <string name="vzw_verify_switch_ssn">[Ûšé Šöçîåļ Šéçûŕîţý ñûḿɓéŕ îñšţéåð one two three four]</string>
    <string name="vzw_verify_title">[νéŕîƒý ýöûŕ åççöûñţ one two three]</string>
</resources>
