<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="abc_action_bar_home_description">[ÑåVîĝåţé ĥöḿé one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_action_bar_up_description">[ÑåVîĝåţé ûþ one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_action_menu_overflow_description">[Ḿöŕé öþţîöñš one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_action_mode_done">[Ðöñé one]</string>
    <string name="abc_activity_chooser_view_see_all">[Šéé åļļ one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_activitychooserview_choose_application">[Çĥööšé åñ åþþ one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_capital_off">[ÖFF one]</string>
    <string name="abc_capital_on">[ÖÑ one]</string>
    <string name="abc_font_family_body_1_material">[šåñš-šéŕîƒ one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_font_family_body_2_material">[šåñš-šéŕîƒ-ḿéðîûḿ one two three]</string>
    <string name="abc_font_family_button_material">[šåñš-šéŕîƒ-ḿéðîûḿ one two three]</string>
    <string name="abc_font_family_caption_material">[šåñš-šéŕîƒ one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_font_family_display_1_material">[šåñš-šéŕîƒ one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_font_family_display_2_material">[šåñš-šéŕîƒ one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_font_family_display_3_material">[šåñš-šéŕîƒ one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_font_family_display_4_material">[šåñš-šéŕîƒ-ļîĝĥţ one two three]</string>
    <string name="abc_font_family_headline_material">[šåñš-šéŕîƒ one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_font_family_menu_material">[šåñš-šéŕîƒ one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_font_family_subhead_material">[šåñš-šéŕîƒ one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_font_family_title_material">[šåñš-šéŕîƒ-ḿéðîûḿ one two three]</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_alt_shortcut_label">[Åļţ+ one]</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_ctrl_shortcut_label">[Çţŕļ+ one]</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_delete_shortcut_label">[ðéļéţé one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_enter_shortcut_label">[éñţéŕ one]</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_function_shortcut_label">[Fûñçţîöñ+ one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_meta_shortcut_label">[Ḿéţå+ one]</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_shift_shortcut_label">[Šĥîƒţ+ one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_space_shortcut_label">[šþåçé one]</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_sym_shortcut_label">[Šýḿ+ one]</string>
    <string name="abc_prepend_shortcut_label">[Ḿéñû+ one]</string>
    <string name="abc_search_hint">[Šéåŕçĥ… one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_clear">[Çļéåŕ Qûéŕý one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_query">[Šéåŕçĥ Qûéŕý one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_search">[Šéåŕçĥ one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_submit">[Šûɓḿîţ Qûéŕý one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_voice">[νöîçé šéåŕçĥ one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_shareactionprovider_share_with">[Šĥåŕé ŵîţĥ one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_shareactionprovider_share_with_application">[Šĥåŕé ŵîţĥ %s one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_toolbar_collapse_description">[Çöļļåþšé one two]</string>
    <string name="app_label">[νöŴîFî ÅçţîVåţîöñ one two three]</string>
    <string name="apt_suite_number">[Åþţ, Šûîţé, éţç. one two three]</string>
    <string name="button_setup_web_portal">[Çöñţîñûé Šéţûþ one two three]</string>
    <string name="button_turn_on_wifi">[Ţûŕñ öñ Ŵî-Fî one two]</string>
    <string name="cancel">[Çåñçéļ one two]</string>
    <string name="city">[Çîţý one]</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_enable_button">[Éñåɓļé one two]</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_enable_text">"[%1$s ŵöñ'ţ ŵöŕķ ûñļéšš ýöû éñåɓļé Ĝööĝļé Þļåý šéŕVîçéš. one two three four five six]"</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_enable_title">[Éñåɓļé Ĝööĝļé Þļåý šéŕVîçéš one two three four]</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_install_button">[Îñšţåļļ one two]</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_install_text">"[%1$s ŵöñ'ţ ŕûñ ŵîţĥöûţ Ĝööĝļé Þļåý šéŕVîçéš, ŵĥîçĥ åŕé ḿîššîñĝ ƒŕöḿ ýöûŕ ðéVîçé. one two three four five six seven eight]"</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_install_title">[Ĝéţ Ĝööĝļé Þļåý šéŕVîçéš one two three]</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_notification_ticker">[Ĝööĝļé Þļåý šéŕVîçéš éŕŕöŕ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_unknown_issue">[%1$s îš ĥåVîñĝ ţŕöûɓļé ŵîţĥ Ĝööĝļé Þļåý šéŕVîçéš. Þļéåšé ţŕý åĝåîñ. one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_unsupported_text">"[%1$s ŵöñ'ţ ŕûñ ŵîţĥöûţ Ĝööĝļé Þļåý šéŕVîçéš, ŵĥîçĥ åŕé ñöţ šûþþöŕţéð ɓý ýöûŕ ðéVîçé. one two three four five six seven eight nine]"</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_update_button">[Ûþðåţé one two]</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_update_text">"[%1$s ŵöñ'ţ ŕûñ ûñļéšš ýöû ûþðåţé Ĝööĝļé Þļåý šéŕVîçéš. one two three four five six]"</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_update_title">[Ûþðåţé Ĝööĝļé Þļåý šéŕVîçéš one two three four]</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_updating_text">"[%1$s ŵöñ'ţ ŕûñ ŵîţĥöûţ Ĝööĝļé Þļåý šéŕVîçéš, ŵĥîçĥ åŕé çûŕŕéñţļý ûþðåţîñĝ. one two three four five six seven eight]"</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_wear_update_text">[Ñéŵ Véŕšîöñ öƒ Ĝööĝļé Þļåý šéŕVîçéš ñééðéð. Îţ ŵîļļ ûþðåţé îţšéļƒ šĥöŕţļý. one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="common_open_on_phone">[Öþéñ öñ þĥöñé one two]</string>
    <string name="common_signin_button_text">[Šîĝñ îñ one two]</string>
    <string name="common_signin_button_text_long">[Šîĝñ îñ ŵîţĥ Ĝööĝļé one two three]</string>
    <string name="connect_to_wifi_or_web_portal_message">[Ýöû çåñ šéţ ûþ Ŵî-Fî çåļļîñĝ ûšîñĝ ţĥé ḿöɓîļé ñéţŵöŕķ, ɓûţ ýöû’ļļ ñééð ţö ţûŕñ öñ Ŵî-Fî åñð çöññéçţ ţö å ñéţŵöŕķ ţö ûšé ţĥîš ƒéåţûŕé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three]</string>
    <string name="connect_to_wifi_or_web_portal_title">[Ŵî-Fî îš ţûŕñéð öƒƒ one two three]</string>
    <string name="edit_address">[Éðîţ Åððŕéšš one two]</string>
    <string name="emergency_address_app_label">[Éḿéŕĝéñçý Åððŕéšš Ḿåñåĝéḿéñţ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="failure_contact_carrier">[Þļéåšé çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ çåŕŕîéŕ ţö éñåɓļé Ŵî-Fî çåļļîñĝ. one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="house_number">[Åððŕéšš Ñûḿɓéŕ one two three]</string>
    <string name="ok">[ÖĶ one]</string>
    <string name="progress_text">[Þļéåšé ŵåîţ… one two three]</string>
    <string name="save">[ŠåVé one]</string>
    <string name="save_anyway">[ŠåVé Åñýŵåý one two]</string>
    <string name="search_menu_title">[Šéåŕçĥ one two]</string>
    <string name="state">[Šţåţé one]</string>
    <string name="status_bar_notification_info_overflow">[999+ one]</string>
    <string name="street">[Šţŕééţ one two]</string>
    <string name="suw_back_button_label">[βåçķ one]</string>
    <string name="suw_more_button_label">[Ḿöŕé one]</string>
    <string name="suw_next_button_label">[Ñéхţ one]</string>
    <string name="tos_continue">[Çöñţîñûé one two]</string>
    <string name="vzw_address_alternate_text">[Ðîð ýöû ḿéåñ: one two]</string>
    <string name="vzw_address_confirm_text_part1">[Ŵé çöûļð ñöţ ƒîñð ţĥé åððŕéšš ţĥåţ ýöû éñţéŕéð ɓéçåûšé ţĥé šţŕééţ åððŕéšš çöûļð ñöţ ɓé ƒöûñð, öŕ ţĥé çîţý, šţåţé, åñð žîþ çöðé ḿåý ñöţ ɓé çöŕŕéçţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="vzw_address_confirm_text_part2">[Îƒ ýöûŕ çîţý, šţåţé, åñð žîþ åŕé ñöţ çöŕŕéçţ ţåþ %1$s, öţĥéŕŵîšé ţåþ %2$s. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="vzw_address_select_text">[Ŵé çöûļð ñöţ ƒîñð ţĥé åððŕéšš ţĥåţ ýöû éñţéŕéð: one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="vzw_address_update_error">[Ûñåɓļé ţö ûþðåţé ţĥé çûŕŕéñţ éḿéŕĝéñçý åððŕéšš åţ ţĥîš ţîḿé. Þļéåšé ţŕý åĝåîñ ļåţéŕ. one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="vzw_address_update_success_toast">[Éḿéŕĝéñçý åððŕéšš ûþðåţéð one two three]</string>
    <string name="vzw_e911_description">[<b>ÎḾÞÖŔŢÅÑŢ - ÉḾÉŔĜÉÑÇÝ 911 ÅÐÐŔÉŠŠ ŔÉqÛÎŔÉÐ</b>"
Ţö ţûŕñ öñ Ŵî-Fî Çåļļîñĝ, éñţéŕ ţĥé Û.Š. åððŕéšš ŵĥéŕé ýöû ŵåñţ éḿéŕĝéñçý šéŕVîçéš šéñţ îƒ ýöû çåļļ 911. Ýöû çåñ ĝö ţö Šéţţîñĝš åñð çĥåñĝé ţĥîš åððŕéšš åţ åñý ţîḿé. Îţ îš Véŕý îḿþöŕţåñţ ţö ûþðåţé ţĥîš åððŕéšš ŵĥéñéVéŕ ýöû çĥåñĝé ýöûŕ ļöçåţîöñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight]"</string>
    <string name="vzw_e911_title">[Éḿéŕĝéñçý Ļöçåţîöñ Îñƒöŕḿåţîöñ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="vzw_e911_warning">[<b>ŴÅŔÑÎÑĜŠ - ÉḾÉŔĜÉÑÇÝ 911 ÇÅĻĻ ĻÎḾÎŢÅŢÎÖÑŠ</b>"
Ŵĥéñ çåļļîñĝ 911, åļŵåýš ţéļļ ţĥé öþéŕåţöŕ ŵĥéŕé ýöû åŕé. Ýöûŕ 911 çåļļ ŵîļļ ĝö öVéŕ Ŵî-Fî öñļý îƒ ţĥé ḿöɓîļé ñéţŵöŕķ îš ûñåVåîļåɓļé. 911 çåļļ ḿåðé öVéŕ Ŵî-Fî ḿåý ɓé ðéļåýéð öŕ ûñšûççéššƒûļ; ƒöŕ éхåḿþļé, îƒ ţĥé 911 šýšţéḿ ðöéšñ'ţ ŕéçöĝñîžé ţĥé åððŕéšš, éļéçţŕîçåļ þöŵéŕ îš öûţ, öŕ ýöûŕ Ŵî-Fî çöññéçţîöñ îšñ'ţ ŵöŕķîñĝ. Éḿéŕĝéñçý šéŕVîçéš ŵîļļ ɓé šéñţ ţö ţĥé åððŕéšš ýöû þŕöVîðéð åɓöVé, šö þļéåšé ûþðåţé îţ åš ýöû çĥåñĝé ļöçåţîöñš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen]"</string>
    <string name="vzw_partial_confirm_head">[Ţĥé åððŕéšš éñţéŕéð çöûļð ñöţ ɓé Våļîðåţéð ɓý Éḿéŕĝéñçý ŠéŕVîçé ÞŕöVîðéŕš. one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="vzw_partial_confirm_text">[Åŕé ýöû šûŕé ýöû ŵåñţ ţö ûšé ţĥîš åððŕéšš îñ çåšé öƒ åñ éḿéŕĝéñçý¿ one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="vzw_partial_failure_text_part1">[Ţĥé çîţý, šţåţé, öŕ žîþ çöðé ţĥåţ ýöû éñţéŕéð ḿåý ñöţ ɓé çöŕŕéçţ. one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="vzw_partial_failure_text_part2">[Þļéåšé çĥéçķ ţĥé åððŕéšš åñð ţŕý åĝåîñ. one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="vzw_tos_link">[Ţéŕḿš åñð Çöñðîţîöñš one two three]</string>
    <string name="vzw_tos_text">"[Ŵî-Fî Çåļļîñĝ ļéţš ýöû ţö ḿåķé çåļļš ûšîñĝ Ŵî-Fî ŵĥéñ ţĥé ḿöɓîļé ñéţŵöŕķ îš ñöţ åVåîļåɓļé.

Ţö šéţ ûþ Ŵî-Fî Çåļļîñĝ, ýöû ŵîļļ ñééð ţö éñţéŕ å ÛŠ åððŕéšš. Ţĥîš åððŕéšš ŵîļļ ɓé ûšéð ɓý éḿéŕĝéñçý šéŕVîçéš îñ ýöûŕ ļöçåţîöñ îƒ ýöû ḿåķé åñ éḿéŕĝéñçý (É911) çåļļ öVéŕ Ŵî-Fî ƒŕöḿ ţĥîš þĥöñé ŵîţĥîñ ţĥé ÛŠ.

Ŵé ŕéçöḿḿéñð ýöû çĥåñĝé ţĥîš åððŕéšš ŵĥéñ ýöû ḿåķé çåļļš ûšîñĝ å ðîƒƒéŕéñţ Ŵî-Fî ñéţŵöŕķ šö ýöûŕ ļöçåţîöñ îñƒöŕḿåţîöñ îš åççûŕåţé. Ýöû çåñ çĥåñĝé ýöûŕ ļöçåţîöñ åñý ţîḿé ɓý ĝöîñĝ ţö Ŵî-Fî Çåļļîñĝ šéţţîñĝš ḿéñû. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three]"</string>
    <string name="vzw_tos_title">[ÅçţîVåţé Ŵî-Fî Çåļļîñĝ one two three]</string>
    <string name="vzw_wfc_activation_error">[Ûñåɓļé ţö åçţîVåţé Ŵî-Fî çåļļîñĝ. Þļéåšé ţŕý åĝåîñ ļåţéŕ. one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="zip_code">[Žîþ çöðé one two]</string>
</resources>
