<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="auth_account_module_display_name">Google accounts</string>
    <string name="auth_account_removed_default_title">Setup cancelled</string>
    <string name="auth_account_removed_dm_setup_skipped_title">Setup cancelled</string>
    <string name="auth_account_removed_restricted_by_admin_description">"Only one managed account is allowed for this device. If you have questions, contact your organisation's admin."</string>
    <string name="auth_account_setup_title">Google account</string>
    <string name="auth_cant_add_work_account_message">This type of account is managed by your organisation.</string>
    <string name="auth_captcha_instructions">Type the text that you see here:</string>
    <string name="auth_common_go_back">Go back</string>
    <string name="auth_device_management_download_description_kids">To add the account to this device, first install <b>^1</b>". 

^1 helps you set up this device for your child."</string>
    <string name="auth_device_management_download_skip_message_nonskippable">Adding this account requires device management. Would you like to start afresh with a different account?</string>
    <string name="auth_device_management_screenlock_description">"To access your work account on this device, you'll need to set a lock screen. This is your organisation's mobile device policy."</string>
    <string name="auth_device_management_screenlock_skip_message">This account requires Screen Lock security. Would you like to start again with a different account?</string>
    <string name="auth_device_management_setup_work_profile_description">"Your work profile keeps your work apps separate and is managed by your organisation.

To finish setup, you’ll need a code from your IT admin. A management tool will be downloaded and used by your IT admin to manage your work profile."</string>
    <string name="auth_device_management_setup_work_profile_enrollment_link_description">"Your work profile keeps your work apps separate and is managed by your organisation.

A management tool will be downloaded and used by your IT admin to manage your work profile."</string>
    <string name="auth_device_management_start_description_kids">To add the account to this device, use <b>^1</b>". 

^1 helps you set up this device for your child."</string>
    <string name="auth_device_management_update_description_kids">To add the account to this device, first install the latest version of <b>^1</b>". 

^1 helps you set up this device for your child."</string>
    <string name="auth_doesnt_use_gmail">" "<b>^1</b>" doesn't use Gmail."</string>
    <string name="auth_error_needs_browser">To access your account, you must sign in online. Tap Next to start browser sign in.</string>
    <string name="auth_frp_device_managed_label">This device has been set up to be managed by your organisation.</string>
    <string name="auth_frp_preadd_lkscreen_text">Your device was factory reset. You can unlock it with your previous secret.</string>
    <string name="auth_get_token_bad_auth_work_service_account_message">"This account couldn't be accessed. Make sure that your device is following your organisation's security policies. If you keep seeing this error, contact your organisation's admin."</string>
    <string name="auth_gls_dmagent_activity_download_message">" Your domain requires mobile device management. Install the \"Google Apps Device Policy\" app to enforce the security policies required by the  "<b>^1</b> account.</string>
    <string name="auth_gls_hint_illegal_chars">" "<b>^1</b>" can contain only letters,
numbers and full stops."</string>
    <string name="auth_gls_hint_numbers_only">" "<b>^1</b>" doesn't contain any letters."</string>
    <string name="auth_gls_hint_size">" "<b>^1</b> contains fewer than 6 or more than 30 characters.</string>
    <string name="auth_gls_is_not_available">The username <b>^1</b>" isn't available."</string>
    <string name="auth_gls_third_party_activity_download_message">" The account  "<b>^1</b> must be added to a device or work profile administered by your organisation. Please follow the instructions provided by your IT admin in order to complete this.</string>
    <string name="auth_invalid_login_character">Invalid character. Only 0-9, a-z, A-Z and full stops are allowed.</string>
    <string name="auth_invalid_username">"The text you have typed isn't a valid username."</string>
    <string name="auth_login_activity_loginfail_text_pwonly">You typed an incorrect password or your account has changed. Re-type your password. If you forgot your password and need to recover your account click <annotation id="help_url">here</annotation>.</string>
    <string name="auth_no_network_help">This could be a temporary problem or your Android device may not be provisioned for data services. Try again when connected to a mobile network or connect to a Wi-Fi network.</string>
    <string name="auth_otp_ten_digit_explaination">"If you forget your password or you're signing in from a new device or location, you may be asked for one or both of these codes to help protect your Google account."</string>
    <string name="auth_otp_ten_digit_phishing_warning">"These codes expire 15 minutes from now or after they're used. You should only use them on web pages with URLs that start with 'https://accounts.google.com/'."</string>
    <string name="auth_relogin_activity_title">Retype password</string>
    <string name="auth_remove_account_start_over">Start Again</string>
    <string name="auth_setup_wizard_account_added_activity_title">Account added</string>
    <string name="auth_sign_in_agreement">By signing in, you agree to the <annotation id="google_privacy">Google</annotation> and <annotation id="android_privacy">Additional</annotation> Privacy Policies.</string>
    <string name="auth_sign_in_with_google_account_short">Sign in with your Google account:</string>
    <string name="auth_ui_activity_title_browser_signin">Sign in</string>
    <string name="auth_ui_add_account_title">Account set up</string>
    <string name="auth_uncertified_notification_description"><b>Users who purchased this device:</b>"
The device manufacturer has preloaded Google apps and services without certification from Google. Contact the manufacturer and ask for a certified device. Learn more at g.co/AndroidCertifiedDevice.

"<b>Unlicensed manufacturers:</b>"
You need a licence from Google to distribute Google apps and services. Apply at g.co/AndroidGMSContact.

"<b>Licensed manufacturers:</b>"
To use Google apps and services during development, register the device. Contact your Google Business Development Manager for more info.

"<b>Custom ROM users:</b>"
To use Google apps and services with a custom ROM, register this device. Learn more at g.co/apps-custom."</string>
    <string name="authorization_dialog">Authorisation dialogue</string>
    <string name="common_add_account_label">Add an account.</string>
    <string name="common_connected_apps_settings_title">Apps connected</string>
    <string name="common_connecting">Connecting …</string>
    <string name="common_get_started">Get started.</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_wrong_architecture_text">Google Play services have been installed with an architecture (%1$s) that is different from your device architecture (%2$s).</string>
    <string name="common_learn_more">Find out more</string>
    <string name="common_loading">Loading …</string>
    <string name="common_missing_url_viewer">Missing viewer to show an external URL.</string>
    <string name="common_network_unavailable">No Internet connection</string>
    <string name="common_no_thanks">No, thanks</string>
    <string name="common_open_source_licenses">Open-source licences</string>
    <string name="common_privacy_policy_composed_string">Privacy policy</string>
    <string name="common_signin_button_text">Sign In</string>
    <string name="common_terms_of_service">Terms of Service</string>
    <string name="common_terms_of_service_composed_string">Terms of service</string>
    <string name="common_url_load_unsuccessful_message_wifi_only">"Your Android device isn't connected to a Wi-Fi network. To view this information now, visit %s via a web browser."</string>
    <string name="continue_to_login_heading">Please log in</string>
    <string name="continue_to_login_text">Credentials granted. Proceed to log in on your first device.</string>
    <string name="fido_ble_dont_see_your_key_dialog_message">"Press and hold the button on your key for at least 5 seconds to make sure that it's in pairing mode"</string>
    <string name="fido_ble_pair_device_pairing">Pairing your Security Key...</string>
    <string name="fido_ble_pair_instructions_body">Pair your key to this device so that you can use it with your account</string>
    <string name="fido_ble_select_device_body">From the list below select the Security Key that you wish to pair with your device. The name may be printed on the back of the key.</string>
    <string name="fido_paask_body">A nearby device is trying to sign in with your Google account</string>
    <string name="fido_paask_footer">This is an enhanced sign-in protection using an encrypted Bluetooth connection to a nearby device.</string>
    <string name="fido_processing">Verifying your Security Key...</string>
    <string name="fido_transport_selection_body">Security Keys work with Bluetooth, NFC and USB. Choose how you want to use your key.</string>
    <string name="fingerprint_description">"Confirm your fingerprint so %1$s can verify that it's you."</string>
    <string name="fingerprint_not_recognized">Fingerprint not recognised. Try again</string>
    <string name="fingerprint_success">Fingerprint recognised</string>
    <string name="permgrouplab_phone">Telephone</string>
    <string name="permgrouplab_sensors">Body sensors</string>
    <string name="plus_oob_interstitial_loading_text">This may take a few minutes.</string>
    <string name="setupservices_google_services_agreement">By continuing, you agree that this device may also automatically download and install updates and apps from Google, your operator and your device’s manufacturer, possibly using mobile data. Some of these apps may offer in-app purchases. You can remove these apps at any time.</string>
    <string name="setupservices_google_services_agreement_dialog_text">To remove apps, go to Settings > Apps or Application manager. Then tap the app that you want to uninstall (you may need to swipe right or left to find the app). Then tap Uninstall or Disable.</string>
    <string name="setupservices_google_services_agreement_korea">You also hereby consent and grant preloaded Google apps permission to access information and functions on your device. See <annotation link="app_permissions">this page</annotation> for more information on usage of these permissions.</string>
    <string name="setupservices_google_services_automatic_storage_manager">When your phone storage is almost full, free space by removing data, such as backed-up photos and videos.</string>
    <string name="setupservices_google_services_backup">Easily restore your data or switch phones at any time. Your backup includes apps, app data and device settings (including Wi‑Fi passwords).</string>
    <string name="setupservices_google_services_backup_dialog_text">"^1

Backup data will not count towards your Drive storage quota."</string>
    <string name="setupservices_google_services_backup_dialog_text_app_data">App data can be any data that an app has saved (based on developer settings), including potentially sensitive data such as contacts, messages and photos.</string>
    <string name="setupservices_google_services_backup_dialog_text_with_photos">"^1

Photos and videos on this device sync to your Google Photos library so that you can search, edit, delete and share from any of your devices. By default, full-resolution photos and videos are uploaded to Google Photos.

Backup data will not count towards your Drive storage quota."</string>
    <string name="setupservices_google_services_backup_v23">Easily restore your data or switch phones at any time. Your backup includes apps, app data, call history, contacts and device settings (including Wi‑Fi passwords and permissions).</string>
    <string name="setupservices_google_services_backup_v26">Easily restore your data or switch phones at any time. Your backup includes apps, app data, call history, contacts, device settings (including Wi‑Fi passwords and permissions) and SMS.</string>
    <string name="setupservices_google_services_backup_v26_with_photos">Easily restore your data or switch phones at any time. Your backup includes apps, app data, call history, contacts, device settings (including Wi‑Fi passwords and permissions), photos, videos and SMS. Photos and videos sync to your Google Photos library and may be used across services.</string>
    <string name="setupservices_google_services_data_policy">Data will be used according to Google’s <annotation link="google_privacy">Privacy Policy</annotation>.</string>
    <string name="setupservices_google_services_data_policy_korea">Data will be used according to Google’s <annotation link="google_privacy">Privacy Policy</annotation> (including <annotation link="additional_privacy">collection, storage and usage of personal information</annotation>) and the <annotation link="location_tos">Location Terms of Service</annotation>.</string>
    <string name="setupservices_google_services_description">Tap to find out more about each service, such as how to turn it on or off later. ^1</string>
    <string name="setupservices_google_services_instant_apps_learn_more">"App details including in-app purchases can be found in the Play Store. App data &amp; settings sync to devices signed in with your Google Account. 

Use of instant apps is governed by the "<a href="https://play.google.com/about/play-terms.html">Google Play Terms of Service</a>". 
"<a href="https://support.google.com/googleplay/?p=instant_apps">Learn more</a>.</string>
    <string name="setupservices_google_services_location_sharing_details_v28">"Google’s Location Service uses sources such as Wi‑Fi, mobile networks and sensors to help estimate your device’s location.

You can turn off location by turning off the main location setting on your device. You can also turn off the use of Wi‑Fi, mobile networks and sensors for location in location settings."</string>
    <string name="setupservices_google_services_location_wireless_scan">"Allow apps and services to scan for Wi‑Fi, even when it's off."</string>
    <string name="setupservices_google_services_tos">If you continue, you also agree to the <annotation link="tos">Google Terms of Service</annotation>.</string>
    <string name="setupservices_google_services_tos_agree">"By clicking the 'I agree' button, you agree to the processing described above for these Google services."</string>
    <string name="setupservices_google_services_tos_germany">When you use this device we abide by our <annotation link="google_privacy">Privacy Policy</annotation> and <annotation link="tos">additional terms</annotation> apply.</string>
    <string name="setupservices_google_services_usage_reporting">Help improve your Android experience by automatically sending diagnostic, device and app usage data to Google. This will help improve battery life, app stability, network connectivity and more. If you turned on additional Web &amp; App Activity, this information will be stored with your account so that you can manage it in My Activity.</string>
    <string name="setupservices_google_services_usage_reporting_details">"This is general information about your device and how you use it (such as battery level, app usage and network connectivity). The data will be used to improve Google’s products and services for everyone. Some aggregated information will help partners, such as Android developers, make their apps and products better too.

Turning off this feature doesn’t affect your device’s ability to send the information needed for essential services such as system updates and security."</string>
    <string name="setupservices_google_services_wallpaper_permission">Allow Google Live wallpapers to respond to your location by accessing Google’s Location Service.</string>
    <string name="setupservices_google_services_wallpaper_permission_details">You can turn access to Google’s Location Service for live wallpapers on or off by going to Settings > Apps &amp; notifications > App info. In the overflow menu, tap Show system > Live data wallpapers or Live Earth Wallpapers > Permissions.</string>
    <string name="setupservices_kids_google_services_agreement">By continuing, you agree that this device may also automatically download and install updates and apps from Google, your operator and this device’s manufacturer, possibly using mobile data. Some of these apps may offer in-app purchases. You can remove these apps at any time.</string>
    <string name="setupservices_kids_google_services_backup">Easily restore data or switch phones at any time. This backup includes apps, app data and device settings (including Wi‑Fi passwords).</string>
    <string name="setupservices_kids_google_services_backup_dialog_text_with_photos">"^1

Photos and videos on this device sync to your child’s Google Photos library so that your child can search, edit, delete and share from any of their devices. By default, full-resolution photos and videos are uploaded to Google Photos.

Backup data will not count towards your child’s Drive storage quota."</string>
    <string name="setupservices_kids_google_services_backup_v23">Easily restore data or switch phones at any time. This backup includes apps, app data, call history, contacts and device settings (including Wi‑Fi passwords and permissions).</string>
    <string name="setupservices_kids_google_services_backup_v26">Easily restore data or switch phones at any time. This backup includes apps, app data, call history, contacts, device settings (including Wi‑Fi passwords and permissions) and SMS.</string>
    <string name="setupservices_kids_google_services_backup_v26_with_photos">Easily restore data or switch phones at any time. This backup includes apps, app data, call history, contacts, device settings (including Wi‑Fi passwords and permissions), photos, videos and SMS. Photos and videos sync to your child’s Google Photos library and may be used across services.</string>
    <string name="setupservices_kids_google_services_location_sharing_details_v28">"Google’s Location Service uses sources such as Wi‑Fi, mobile networks and sensors to help estimate this device’s location.

You can turn off location by turning off the main location setting on this device. You can also turn off the use of Wi‑Fi, mobile networks and sensors for location in location settings."</string>
    <string name="setupservices_kids_google_services_usage_reporting">Help improve Android by automatically sending diagnostic, device and app usage data to Google. This won’t be used to identify your child and will help improve battery life, app stability, network connectivity and more. If additional Web &amp; App Activity is turned on for your child, this information will be stored with your child’s account.</string>
    <string name="setupservices_kids_google_services_usage_reporting_details">"This is general information about this device and how it’s used (such as battery level, app usage and network connectivity). The data will be used to improve Google’s products and services for everyone. Some aggregated information will help partners, such as Android developers, make their apps and products better too.

Turning off this feature doesn’t affect this device’s ability to send the information needed for essential services such as system updates and security."</string>
    <string name="smartdevice_action_try_another_way">Try another way</string>
    <string name="smartdevice_action_turn_on_location">Turn on Location</string>
    <string name="smartdevice_alert_exit_setup_message">Are you sure that you want to exit the setup of your other device?</string>
    <string name="smartdevice_alert_exit_setup_title">Exit device setup?</string>
    <string name="smartdevice_alert_no_accounts_generic_text">To set up your device, you need at least one Google account.</string>
    <string name="smartdevice_alert_no_accounts_text">To set up your %s, you need at least one Google account.</string>
    <string name="smartdevice_alert_quit_button">Exit</string>
    <string name="smartdevice_alert_start_over_button">Start again</string>
    <string name="smartdevice_d2d_fingerprint_not_recognized_text">Not recognised</string>
    <string name="smartdevice_d2d_fingerprint_verification_text">For security reasons, confirm your fingerprint. Your Google accounts, apps and data will be copied to your %s.</string>
    <string name="smartdevice_d2d_source_pin_verification_different_code_dialog_message">Restart setup and choose your ^1 to make sure that you copy your Google Accounts, apps and data to the right device.</string>
    <string name="smartdevice_d2d_source_pin_verification_different_code_link">"Can't see the code?"</string>
    <string name="smartdevice_d2d_source_setup_success">Almost finished!</string>
    <string name="smartdevice_d2d_target_choice_use_old_device">Copy Google accounts, apps and data from your other device</string>
    <string name="smartdevice_d2d_target_google_settings_description">On your other device:&lt;br/>&lt;br/> 1. Open the &lt;b>Google Settings&lt;/b> app&lt;br/>&lt;br/> 2. Select &lt;b>&lt;xliff:g id=set_up_nearby_device_setting_title example=Set up nearby device>%1$s&lt;/xliff:g>&lt;/b> &lt;br/>&lt;br/> 3. Touch &lt;b>&lt;xliff:g id=device_name>%2$s&lt;/xliff:g>&lt;/b> on the list and follow the on-screen instructions</string>
    <string name="smartdevice_d2d_target_skip_primary_account_alert_cancel_button">"Don't skip"</string>
    <string name="smartdevice_d2d_target_skip_primary_account_alert_message">"Setup won't copy this account or backed-up apps and data to this device."</string>
    <string name="smartdevice_magicwand_consent_detail">Tap <b>Sign in</b> to finish signing in to another device.</string>
    <string name="smartdevice_magicwand_lockscreen_description">This extra step helps to make sure that this is a secure device.</string>
    <string name="smartdevice_wifi_cannot_connect_description">Only open networks and WPA/WPA2 networks can be used to set up this device</string>
    <string name="smartdevice_wifi_unavailable_due_to_location_title">"Can't Search for Wi-Fi Networks"</string>
    <string name="verify_your_identity_description">"%1$s needs to verify that it's you."</string>
</resources>
