<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="auth_google_play_services_client_google_display_name">[Ĝööĝļé one two]</string>
    <string name="auth_google_play_services_client_facebook_display_name">[Fåçéɓööķ one two]</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_notification_ticker">[Ĝööĝļé Þļåý šéŕVîçéš éŕŕöŕ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_notification_needs_update_title">[Åñ åþþļîçåţîöñ ŕéQûîŕéš åñ ûþðåţé ƒöŕ Ĝööĝļé Þļåý šéŕVîçéš. one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="common_android_wear_notification_needs_update_text">[%1$s ŕéQûîŕéš åñ ûþðåţé ţö ţĥé Åñðŕöîð Ŵéåŕ åþþ. one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_needs_enabling_title">[Åñ åþþļîçåţîöñ ŕéQûîŕéš Ĝööĝļé Þļåý šéŕVîçéš ţö ɓé éñåɓļéð. one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_error_notification_requested_by_msg">[ŔéQûéšţéð ɓý %1$s one two]</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_install_title">[Ĝéţ Ĝööĝļé Þļåý šéŕVîçéš one two three]</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_install_text_phone">"[%1$s ŵöñ'ţ ŕûñ ŵîţĥöûţ Ĝööĝļé Þļåý šéŕVîçéš, ŵĥîçĥ åŕé ḿîššîñĝ ƒŕöḿ ýöûŕ þĥöñé. one two three four five six seven eight]"</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_install_text_tablet">"[%1$s ŵöñ'ţ ŕûñ ŵîţĥöûţ Ĝööĝļé Þļåý šéŕVîçéš, ŵĥîçĥ åŕé ḿîššîñĝ ƒŕöḿ ýöûŕ ţåɓļéţ. one two three four five six seven eight]"</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_install_button">[Ĝéţ Ĝööĝļé Þļåý šéŕVîçéš one two three]</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_enable_title">[Éñåɓļé Ĝööĝļé Þļåý šéŕVîçéš one two three four]</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_enable_text">"[%1$s ŵöñ'ţ ŵöŕķ ûñļéšš ýöû éñåɓļé Ĝööĝļé Þļåý šéŕVîçéš. one two three four five six]"</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_enable_button">[Éñåɓļé Ĝööĝļé Þļåý šéŕVîçéš one two three four]</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_update_title">[Ûþðåţé Ĝööĝļé Þļåý šéŕVîçéš one two three four]</string>
    <string name="common_android_wear_update_title">[Ûþðåţé Åñðŕöîð Ŵéåŕ one two three]</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_update_text">"[%1$s ŵöñ'ţ ŕûñ ûñļéšš ýöû ûþðåţé Ĝööĝļé Þļåý šéŕVîçéš. one two three four five six]"</string>
    <string name="common_android_wear_update_text">"[%1$s ŵöñ'ţ ŕûñ ûñļéšš ýöû ûþðåţé ţĥé Åñðŕöîð Ŵéåŕ åþþ. one two three four five six]"</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_updating_title">[Ĝööĝļé Þļåý šéŕVîçéš åŕé ûþðåţîñĝ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_updating_text">"[%1$s ŵöñ'ţ ŕûñ ŵîţĥöûţ Ĝööĝļé Þļåý šéŕVîçéš, ŵĥîçĥ åŕé çûŕŕéñţļý ûþðåţîñĝ. one two three four five six seven eight]"</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_network_error_title">[Ñéţŵöŕķ Éŕŕöŕ one two]</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_network_error_text">[Å ðåţå çöññéçţîöñ îš ŕéQûîŕéð ţö çöññéçţ ţö Ĝööĝļé Þļåý šéŕVîçéš. one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_invalid_account_title">[ÎñVåļîð Åççöûñţ one two three]</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_invalid_account_text">[Ţĥé šþéçîƒîéð åççöûñţ ðöéš ñöţ éхîšţ öñ ţĥîš ðéVîçé. Þļéåšé çĥööšé å ðîƒƒéŕéñţ åççöûñţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_unknown_issue">[Ûñķñöŵñ îššûé ŵîţĥ Ĝööĝļé Þļåý šéŕVîçéš. one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_unsupported_title">[Ĝööĝļé Þļåý šéŕVîçéš one two three]</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_unsupported_text">[%1$s ŕéļîéš öñ Ĝööĝļé Þļåý šéŕVîçéš, ŵĥîçĥ îš ñöţ šûþþöŕţéð ɓý ýöûŕ ðéVîçé. Çöñţåçţ ţĥé ḿåñûƒåçţûŕéŕ ƒöŕ åššîšţåñçé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_update_button">[Ûþðåţé one two]</string>
    <string name="common_open_on_phone">[Öþéñ öñ þĥöñé one two]</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_api_unavailable_text">[%1$s ŕéQûîŕéš öñé öŕ ḿöŕé Ĝööĝļé Þļåý šéŕVîçéš ţĥåţ åŕé ñöţ çûŕŕéñţļý åVåîļåɓļé. Þļéåšé çöñţåçţ ţĥé ðéVéļöþéŕ ƒöŕ åššîšţåñçé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_sign_in_failed_title">[Šîĝñ îñ ƒåîļéð one two three]</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_sign_in_failed_text">[Éŕŕöŕ šîĝñîñĝ îñ ţĥé šþéçîƒîéð åççöûñţ. Þļéåšé çĥööšé å ðîƒƒéŕéñţ åççöûñţ. one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="common_signin_button_text">[Šîĝñ îñ one two]</string>
    <string name="common_signin_button_text_long">[Šîĝñ îñ ŵîţĥ Ĝööĝļé one two three]</string>
    <string name="app_name">[Ţŕûšţéð Fåçé one two]</string>
    <string name="trusted_face_service_app_name">[Ţŕûšţéð Fåçé ŠéŕVîçé one two three]</string>
    <string name="receiver_app_name">[Ţŕûšţéð Fåçé βŕöåðçåšţ ŔéçéîVéŕ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="intro_screen_title">[Åɓöûţ ţŕûšţéð ƒåçé one two three]</string>
    <string name="intro_screen_header">[Ûñļöçķ ýöûŕ þĥöñé ɓý ļööķîñĝ åţ îţ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="intro_screen_body_start">"[Ŕéḿéḿɓéŕ:
 one two]"</string>
    <string name="intro_screen_bullets">"[Fåçé ḿåţçĥîñĝ îš ļéšš šéçûŕé ţĥåñ å þåţţéŕñ, ÞÎÑ, öŕ þåššŵöŕð

Šöḿéöñé ŵĥö ļööķš ļîķé ýöû çöûļð ûñļöçķ ýöûŕ þĥöñé

Ţĥé ðåţå ûšéð ţö ŕéçöĝñîžé ýöûŕ ƒåçé îš ķéþţ þŕîVåţé öñ ýöûŕ þĥöñé one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen]"</string>
    <string name="intro_screen_continue_label">[Šéţ ûþ one two]</string>
    <string name="instructions_screen_title">[Åðð å ţŕûšţéð ƒåçé one two three]</string>
    <string name="instructions_screen_header">[Föŕ ɓéšţ ŕéšûļţš: one two three]</string>
    <string name="instructions_screen_bullets">"[Fîñð å šþöţ îñðööŕš ţĥåţ'š ñöţ ţöö ɓŕîĝĥţ öŕ ţöö ðîḿ

Ĥöļð ţĥé þĥöñé åţ éýé ļéVéļ one two three four five six seven eight nine]"</string>
    <string name="instructions_screen_continue_label">[Ñéхţ one]</string>
    <string name="enrollment_screen_title">[Åðð å ţŕûšţéð ƒåçé one two three]</string>
    <string name="enrollment_screen_message_initializing">[Šţåŕţîñĝ ûþ… one two]</string>
    <string name="enrollment_screen_message_initialization_error">"[ Çöûļðñ'ţ šţåŕţ ƒîñðîñĝ ýöûŕ ƒåçé one two three four]"</string>
    <string name="enrollment_screen_message_no_camera_permission_error">"[ Çåḿéŕå þéŕḿîššîöñ îšñ'ţ ĝŕåñţéð one two three four]"</string>
    <string name="enrollment_screen_message_camera_error">"[Çåḿéŕå îšñ'ţ åVåîļåɓļé one two three]"</string>
    <string name="enrollment_start_message">[Ķééþ ƒåçé îñšîðé ðöţţéð åŕéå one two three four]</string>
    <string name="enrollment_screen_message_instructions">[ Ķééþ ţĥé ţöþ öƒ ýöûŕ ĥéåð åñð ţĥé ɓöţţöḿ öƒ ýöûŕ çĥîñ ŵîţĥîñ ţĥé çîŕçļé one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="enrollment_screen_message_done">[Fåçé åððéð one two]</string>
    <string name="enrollment_screen_status_no_face">[Šĥöŵ ýöûŕ ƒåçé one two three]</string>
    <string name="enrollment_screen_status_face_off_center">"[Çåñ'ţ šéé þåŕţ öƒ ýöûŕ ƒåçé one two three four]"</string>
    <string name="enrollment_screen_status_missing_template">"[Çåñ'ţ šéé ýöûŕ ƒéåţûŕéš one two three]"</string>
    <string name="enrollment_screen_continue_label">[Ñéхţ one]</string>
    <string name="enrollment_screen_done_label">[Ðöñé one]</string>
    <string name="enrollment_screen_talkback_preview_description">[Çåḿéŕå þŕéVîéŵ one two three]</string>
    <string name="enrollment_screen_talkback_face_added">[Fåçé åððéð one two]</string>
    <string name="end_screen_title">[Åļļ šéţ¡ one two]</string>
    <string name="end_screen_body">[ Ţö ûñļöçķ ýöûŕ þĥöñé, ĵûšţ ţûŕñ ýöûŕ šçŕééñ öñ åñð ļööķ åţ ţĥé çåḿéŕå one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="end_screen_bullet_one_text">[ Ýöûŕ þĥöñé ŵîļļ ûñļöçķ åš šööñ åš îţ ŕéçöĝñîžéš ýöû one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="end_screen_bullet_two_text">"[ Îƒ ýöûŕ ƒåçé îšñ'ţ ŕéçöĝñîžéð, ûñļöçķ ŵîţĥ ýöûŕ þåţţéŕñ, ÞÎÑ, öŕ þåššŵöŕð îñšţéåð one two three four five six seven eight nine]"</string>
    <string name="end_screen_tip_text">[ Ţîþ: ÎḿþŕöVé ƒåçé ḿåţçĥîñĝ ɓý šĥöŵîñĝ ŵĥåţ ýöû ļööķ ļîķé îñ ðîƒƒéŕéñţ çöñðîţîöñš one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="end_screen_licenses_label">[Ļîçéñšéš one two]</string>
    <string name="end_screen_continue_label">[Ðöñé one]</string>
    <string name="add_to_setup_intro_screen_title">[ÎḿþŕöVé ƒåçé ḿåţçĥîñĝ one two three]</string>
    <string name="add_to_setup_intro_screen_header">[ Šĥöŵ ŵĥåţ ýöû ļööķ ļîķé îñ ðîƒƒéŕéñţ çöñðîţîöñš one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="add_to_setup_intro_screen_body_start">"[Éхåḿþļéš:
 one two]"</string>
    <string name="add_to_setup_intro_screen_bullets">"[Îñ ðîƒƒéŕéñţ ļîĝĥţîñĝ

Ŵîţĥ öŕ ŵîţĥöûţ þŕéšçŕîþţîöñ ĝļåššéš

βéåŕðéð öŕ çļéåñ-šĥåVéñ

 one two three four five six seven eight nine]"</string>
    <string name="add_to_setup_intro_screen_body_end">[Ĥöļð ţĥé þĥöñé åţ éýé ļéVéļ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="add_to_setup_intro_screen_continue_label">[Ñéхţ one]</string>
    <string name="license_screen_title">[Ļîçéñšéš one two]</string>
    <string name="license_screen_header">[Öþéñ šöûŕçé ñöţîçéš one two three]</string>
    <string name="license_screen_continue_label">[ÖĶ one]</string>
    <string name="license_screen_description">"[ Ţĥé 'Ţŕûšţéð ƒåçé' ƒéåţûŕé ḿåý ûšé þöŕţîöñš öƒ ţĥé ƒöļļöŵîñĝ öþéñ šöûŕçé ļîɓŕåŕîéš, ļîçéñšéð ûñðéŕ ţĥé ɓéļöŵ ļîçéñšéš: one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]"</string>
    <string name="license_screen_notices_header">[Ñöţîçéš ƒöŕ ļîɓŕåŕîéš: one two three]</string>
    <string name="license_screen_body">"[ŠŢĻþöŕţ(5.2.1)
 
Çöþýŕîĝĥţ (ç) 1994 
Ĥéŵļéţţ-Þåçķåŕð Çöḿþåñý 
 
Çöþýŕîĝĥţ (ç) 1996-1999 
Šîļîçöñ Ĝŕåþĥîçš Çöḿþûţéŕ Šýšţéḿš, Îñç. 
 
Çöþýŕîĝĥţ (ç) 1997 
Ḿöšçöŵ Çéñţéŕ ƒöŕ ŠÞÅŔÇ Ţéçĥñöļöĝý 
 
Çöþýŕîĝĥţ (ç) 1999-2003 
βöŕîš FöḿîţçĥéV 
 
Ţĥîš ḿåţéŕîåļ îš þŕöVîðéð åš îš, ŵîţĥ åɓšöļûţéļý ñö ŵåŕŕåñţý éхþŕéššéð öŕ îḿþļîéð. Åñý ûšé îš åţ ýöûŕ öŵñ ŕîšķ. 
 
Þéŕḿîššîöñ ţö ûšé öŕ çöþý ţĥîš šöƒţŵåŕé ƒöŕ åñý þûŕþöšé îš ĥéŕéɓý ĝŕåñţéð ŵîţĥöûţ ƒéé, þŕöVîðéð ţĥé åɓöVé ñöţîçéš åŕé ŕéţåîñéð öñ åļļ çöþîéš. Þéŕḿîššîöñ ţö ḿöðîƒý ţĥé çöðé åñð ţö ðîšţŕîɓûţé ḿöðîƒîéð çöðé îš ĝŕåñţéð, þŕöVîðéð ţĥé åɓöVé ñöţîçéš åŕé ŕéţåîñéð, åñð å ñöţîçé ţĥåţ ţĥé çöðé ŵåš ḿöðîƒîéð îš îñçļûðéð ŵîţĥ ţĥé åɓöVé çöþýŕîĝĥţ ñöţîçé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three]"</string>
    <string name="shared_cancel_label">[Çåñçéļ one two]</string>
    <string name="reenrollment_notification_title">[Šḿåŕţ Ļöçķ one two]</string>
    <string name="reenrollment_notification_text">[ Fåçîåļ ŕéçöĝñîţîöñ ĥåš çĥåñĝéð. Åðð ýöûŕ ţŕûšţéð ƒåçé åĝåîñ ţö ķééþ ûšîñĝ îţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
</resources>
