<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="backup_confirm_title">[Fûļļ ɓåçķûþ one two]</string>
    <string name="restore_confirm_title">[Fûļļ ŕéšţöŕé one two]</string>
    <string name="backup_confirm_text">"[Å ƒûļļ ɓåçķûþ öƒ åļļ ðåţå ţö å çöññéçţéð ðéšķţöþ çöḿþûţéŕ ĥåš ɓééñ ŕéQûéšţéð. Ðö ýöû ŵåñţ ţö åļļöŵ ţĥîš ţö ĥåþþéñ?

Îƒ ýöû ðîð ñöţ ŕéQûéšţ ţĥé ɓåçķûþ ýöûŕšéļƒ, ðö ñöţ åļļöŵ ţĥé öþéŕåţîöñ ţö þŕöçééð. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen]"</string>
    <string name="allow_backup_button_label">[βåçķ ûþ ḿý ðåţå one two three]</string>
    <string name="deny_backup_button_label">[Ðö ñöţ ɓåçķ ûþ one two three]</string>
    <string name="restore_confirm_text">"[Å ƒûļļ ŕéšţöŕé öƒ åļļ ðåţå ƒŕöḿ å çöññéçţéð ðéšķţöþ çöḿþûţéŕ ĥåš ɓééñ ŕéQûéšţéð. Ðö ýöû ŵåñţ ţö åļļöŵ ţĥîš ţö ĥåþþéñ?

Îƒ ýöû ðîð ñöţ ŕéQûéšţ ţĥé ŕéšţöŕé ýöûŕšéļƒ, ðö ñöţ åļļöŵ ţĥé öþéŕåţîöñ ţö þŕöçééð. Ţĥîš ŵîļļ ŕéþļåçé åñý ðåţå çûŕŕéñţļý öñ ţĥé ðéVîçé¡ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one]"</string>
    <string name="allow_restore_button_label">[Ŕéšţöŕé ḿý ðåţå one two three]</string>
    <string name="deny_restore_button_label">[Ðö ñöţ ŕéšţöŕé one two three]</string>
    <string name="current_password_text">[Þļéåšé éñţéŕ ýöûŕ çûŕŕéñţ ɓåçķûþ þåššŵöŕð ɓéļöŵ: one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="device_encryption_restore_text">[Þļéåšé éñţéŕ ýöûŕ ðéVîçé éñçŕýþţîöñ þåššŵöŕð ɓéļöŵ. one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="device_encryption_backup_text">[Þļéåšé éñţéŕ ýöûŕ ðéVîçé éñçŕýþţîöñ þåššŵöŕð ɓéļöŵ. Ţĥîš ŵîļļ åļšö ɓé ûšéð ţö éñçŕýþţ ţĥé ɓåçķûþ åŕçĥîVé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="backup_enc_password_text">[Þļéåšé éñţéŕ å þåššŵöŕð ţö ûšé ƒöŕ éñçŕýþţîñĝ ţĥé ƒûļļ ɓåçķûþ ðåţå. Îƒ ţĥîš îš ļéƒţ ɓļåñķ, ýöûŕ çûŕŕéñţ ɓåçķûþ þåššŵöŕð ŵîļļ ɓé ûšéð: one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="backup_enc_password_optional">[Îƒ ýöû ŵîšĥ ţö éñçŕýþţ ţĥé ƒûļļ ɓåçķûþ ðåţå, éñţéŕ å þåššŵöŕð ɓéļöŵ: one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="backup_enc_password_required">[Šîñçé ýöûŕ ðéVîçé îš éñçŕýþţéð, ýöû åŕé ŕéQûîŕéð ţö éñçŕýþţ ýöûŕ ɓåçķûþ. Þļéåšé éñţéŕ å þåššŵöŕð ɓéļöŵ: one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="restore_enc_password_text">[Îƒ ţĥé ŕéšţöŕé ðåţå îš éñçŕýþţéð, þļéåšé éñţéŕ ţĥé þåššŵöŕð ɓéļöŵ: one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="toast_backup_started">[βåçķûþ šţåŕţîñĝ... one two three]</string>
    <string name="toast_backup_ended">[βåçķûþ ƒîñîšĥéð one two three]</string>
    <string name="toast_restore_started">[Ŕéšţöŕé šţåŕţîñĝ... one two three]</string>
    <string name="toast_restore_ended">[Ŕéšţöŕé éñðéð one two]</string>
    <string name="toast_timeout">[Öþéŕåţîöñ ţîḿéð öûţ one two three]</string>
</resources>
