<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="setupservices_google_services_backup">Easily restore your data or switch devices at any time. Your backup includes apps, app data, and device settings (including Wi‑Fi passwords).</string>
    <string name="setupservices_google_services_backup_v23">Easily restore your data or switch devices at any time. Your backup includes apps, app data, call history, contacts, and device settings (including Wi‑Fi passwords and permissions).</string>
    <string name="setupservices_google_services_backup_v26">Easily restore your data or switch devices at any time. Your backup includes apps, app data, call history, contacts, device settings (including Wi‑Fi passwords and permissions), and SMS.</string>
    <string name="setupservices_google_services_backup_v26_with_photos">Easily restore your data or switch devices at any time. Your backup includes apps, app data, call history, contacts, device settings (including Wi‑Fi passwords and permissions), photos, videos, and SMS. Photos and videos sync to your Google Photos library and may be used across services.</string>
    <string name="auth_setup_wizard_services_backup">Easily restore or switch devices at any time. Backup includes apps, app data, and device settings (including Wi‑Fi passwords).</string>
    <string name="auth_setup_wizard_services_backup_v23">Easily restore or switch devices at any time. Backup includes apps, app data, call history, contacts, and device settings (including Wi‑Fi passwords and permissions).</string>
    <string name="auth_setup_wizard_services_backup_v26">Easily restore or switch devices at any time. Backup includes apps, app data, call history, contacts, device settings (including Wi‑Fi passwords and permissions), and SMS.</string>
    <string name="auth_setup_wizard_services_backup_v26_with_photos">Easily restore or switch devices at any time. Backup includes apps, app data, call history, contacts, device settings (including Wi‑Fi passwords and permissions), photos, videos, and SMS. Photos and videos are synced to your Google Account and may be used across services.</string>
</resources>
